thephoenix.com 2016-06-28

# Privacy Policy

Safeguarding your privacy is very important to us. The only personally-identifiable information this website obtains about you is information voluntarily provided by you through our website. On certain pages – such as registration for promotions, email subscription registrations, and comment forums - we may ask users for names, addresses, phone numbers, e-mail address, and demographic and/or personal information. This information is gathered only with the users’ consent.

We will not share any user’s personally-identifiable information with any other organization, nor will we publish such information unless we have your consent, are under a legal order to do so, or there is an emergency involving personal danger.

Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, e-mail addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. We won’t knowingly allow anyone under 13 to register with us or to provide any other personal information. If you’re under 13, please do not provide us with any personal information about yourself (such as your name, your e-mail address or your phone number).

When a user shares our content with a friend through our email forwarding service, the user’s email address will be used only to send the requested content.

Please note that if a user gives out personal information online – for example, if you include your personal website address in a comment posting – that information can be collected and used by third parties. Although we strive to protect our users’ privacy, Phoenix Media cannot guarantee the security of information that users post publicly in these forums. A user is disclosing such information at his or her own risk.

Phoenix Media collects aggregate information site-wide, including non-personally-identifiable site statistics through the use of Google Analytics. We also collect and maintain domain names, IP addresses, and web locations from which users come to our site. This information is used primarily to discover which features users are reading the most, what features they like best, and what we can do to make things better.

We also may analyze the aggregated information and share that data with advertisers (for example, we might track how many users see and click on a particular advertisement).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. We may share non-personally-identifiable information about your visits to this website with these companies (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number). These companies may, in turn, use the information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "Network Advertising Opt-Out").

If we decide to change our policy with respect to our use of your personal information, we will post those changes here. However, this policy has been developed with the understanding that the Internet is rapidly changing and evolving, and therefore information contained in this policy statement relating to actions by third parties are subject to change at any time without notice.

Third-party sites that are accessed through hyperlinks from Phoenix Media sites are not covered by this site’s policies. Phoenix Media is not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites.

The Phoenix website (“thephoenix.com”) is a division of and owned and operated by Phoenix Media/Communications Group, Inc, and is the only operator of this website. You may contact us directly if you have any questions regarding the content and material on our website or if you have any questions about our privacy policy – please send email to:[webmaster@phx.com](mailto:webmaster@phx.com).
